<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Content>
  <Global>
    <FullCompanyName>Flucomp Enterprises, Inc.</FullCompanyName>
    <CompanyDescription>
      We provide programming expertise, custom software solutions and consulting for engineers of all trades. We help you do the best job you can.
    </CompanyDescription>
    <SEOKeywords>cfd, computational fluid dynamics, programming, engineering, unit converter, flucomp</SEOKeywords>
  </Global>
  <Page Name="Footer">
    <Content Name="About">
      <![CDATA[Copyright &copy; 2012-2013 Flucomp Enterprises, Inc.&nbsp;&nbsp;{appversion}&nbsp;]]>
    </Content>
  </Page>
  <Page Name="Home">
    <Content Name="Summary">
      <![CDATA[
			<h3>Our Mission</h3>
<p>As our customer’s advocate we provide cost-effective, long lasting design and solutions in market and technology intelligence spanning 
the Oil & Natural Gas Value Chain and Bio-renewable markets for companies, private investors and research assisting decision makers define strategies.
</p>
]]>
    </Content>
    <Content Name="Focus">
      <![CDATA[
      <h3>Our Focus</h3>
        <p>
            We strive to work as partners with our clients, to best address multi-client research needs with objective data and analyses.
            Our primary focus has been in the complex Oil &amp; Natural Gas Value Chain with near-term and long-term profitability dependent
            on multiple markets &ndash; upstream production, refined products to petrochemical feedstock, power and gas liquids. Our expertise
            has been a foundational-level integration of the technology, research, rapid commercialization of new technology, engineering and understanding
            of the Natural Gas and NGL market to provide our clients with a base to build upon. We go beyond this in recognizing that
            &ldquo;learning to fish is far better than merely giving you the fish&rdquo; by assisting our clients through on-site training to
            understand how to build these models and which metrics to rely on for investment; becoming critical of results and knowing the right questions
            to ask is the foundation of success.
        </p>
      ]]>
    </Content>
    <Content Name="BlogTitle">
      Updates
    </Content>
  </Page>
  <Page Name="Products">
    <Product>
      <Name>AbiConvert</Name>
      <Description>
        <![CDATA[
				<p>Convert the units you need as an engineer, in an easy-to-use interface. </p>
				<p>New units are added often, send us an <a href="mailto:inbox@flucomp.com">email</a> if you think we're missing something!</p>
				]]>
      </Description>
      <Link>~/AbiConvert</Link>
      <Picture>~/Include/img/convertLogo.png</Picture>
    </Product>
    <Product>
      <Name>PipeEngicalc ALPHA</Name>
      <Description>
        <![CDATA[
        <p><b>PipeEngicalc</b> is a comprehensive mechanical pipeline analysis software, which assists with design, analysis, calculations and troubleshooting
        of piping systems; saving time and minimizing operating costs. This is an alpha version for polypropylene pipelines with Steel grades coming soon.</p>
        <p>You are invited to download the fully functional test version of PipeEngicalc now! We truly welcome and appreciate feedback on specific features, 
        and what you would like to see added to this program. We especially appreciate feedback on bugs and errors encountered while using this application.</p>
        ]]>
      </Description>
      <!--<Link>http://cdn.flucomp.com/deploy/setup-engicalc-0.1.0.exe</Link>-->
      <Link>#</Link>
      <Picture>~/Include/img/engicalc.png</Picture>
    </Product>
  </Page>
  <Page Name="Services">
    <Content Name="Index">
      <![CDATA[
				<h3>Our Services</h3>
        <h4>Engineering and Technical Operational Consulting Services</h4>
        <p>
            These are related to plant technical operations, optimization and engineering aspects of the business: 
            assets/hardware rather than the commercial aspects of the business. Example services that may be performed are 
            plant optimization studies, environmental compliance reviews, troubleshooting or “plant triage”, assistance with 
            equipment sizing, advising vendors on marketing plans or product.
        </p>
        <h4>Assistance with Vendors</h4>
        <p>
            As projects move through the Front End Engineering Design Process (FEED) or Front End Loaded (FEL) RFQ/RFP are required. 
            We can assist not only in in putting together the RFPs but also in vendor vetting. 
            This is an important process, because some vendors will try to fit the bid specs or requirements around and into their products.
        </p>
        <h4>Economic Feasibility Studies and Financial Estimates of Capital and Operating Costs</h4>
        <p>
            During technical consulting services, it is often required to create pro forma estimates of plant construction costs, 
            or other financial estimates, that are typically used in final investment decisions to proceed or not to proceed.
        </p>
        <h4>Engineering Software Applications and IT Consulting Services</h4>
        <p>
            Flucomp's Founder, Dr. Diana Matonis, has created engineering and design software tools, which are used around the world on projects
            arnging from GHG plant emissions calculators, small retrofits of existing facilities to large, green-field facilities, whether on land 
            or sea by major multi-national Oil &amp; Gas corporations.
        </p>
        <p>
            We continue our founder's original focus in developing customer-specific and customized computer software and tools that deliver
            high individual and corporate-wide technical know-how and productivity regardless of the systems used.
        </p>]]>
    </Content>
    <Content Name="Engineering">
      <![CDATA[
			<h3>Engineering Consultancy</h3>
			<p>
				Flucomp was founded by Dr. Diana Matonis, a leader in her industry for more than 25 years. Our engineering consultancy
				practice includes our capabilities in plant assessments through the use of process engineering and design, to provide 
				insights of current efficiency and product yield leading to their improvements through new plant technology and startups.
			</p>
			<h3>Example</h3>
			<p>
				We improved the quality, consistency and yield of a product for a startup biofuels company that used a new integrated
				pyrolytic process for obtaining saturated and unsaturated alkyl esters from biomass; we improved their process to the point
				where they were able to produce a consistent biodiesel-grade product.
			</p>
			<h3>Our Process</h3>
			<p>
				In cultivating a robust assessment, evaluation and technology planning, we utilize our skills and experience and have 
				identified and typically use three key phases as a starting point.
			</p>
			<ol>
				<li>
					Iterative Analysis
					<br />
					<ul>
						<li><em>SIPOC</em> (Suppliers, Inputs, Processes, Outputs and Customer) oriented interviews</li>
						<li>Models made based on the results of these interviews</li>
						<li>Modeled processes are reviewed with the process owners and/or stakeholders</li>
					</ul>
				</li>
				<li>
					Model Based Systems Engineering for Value (Value Based)
					<br />
					<ul>
						<li>Translate business practice reality into critical design models and requirement specifications.</li>
						<li>Accurately capture, analyze and verify design integrity before problems become embedded in the system</li>
					</ul>
				</li>
				<li>
					Implementation
					<br />
					<ul>
						<li>Improvements grounded in reality, making them efficient and effective.</li>
						<li>Requirements create an accurate picture of business practice needs.</li>
						<li>Understanding the client's business practices results in a more focused capability development and improvement</li>
						<li>Results are directly traceable to the implemented solutions</li>
					</ul>
				</li>
			</ol>]]>
    </Content>
    <Content Name="Software">
      <![CDATA[
<h3>Software Development Services</h3>
		<p>
			Our team has more than 30 combined years of experience in software development.
			We currently provide the following:
		</p>
		<table id="service_software_table">
			<thead>
				<tr>
					<th>Software</th>
					<th>Mobile Apps</th>
					<th>Web Development</th>
				</tr>
			</thead>
			<tbody>
				<tr>
					<td>
						<ul>
							<li>C/C++ Applications</li>
							<li>C#/.NET Applications</li>
							<li>Windows 8 Applications</li>
							<li>Java Applications</li>
							<li>Database Services: MySQL, Microsoft SQL, SQLite</li>
						</ul>
					</td>
					<td>
						<ul>
							<li>Android Applications in Java</li>
							<li>HTML5 Platform-Independent Mobile Applications</li>
						</ul>
					</td>
					<td>
						<ul>
							<li>Cloud Computing Solutions</li>
							<li>HTML5/JavaScript/jQuery Client-Side Webapps</li>
							<li>PHP/MySQL Sites</li>
						</ul>
					</td>
				</tr>
			</tbody>
		</table>
		<p>
			We have found that by working side-by-side with our clients will produce the best results.
			<br />
			Email us now for a quote: <a href="mailto:vmatonis@flucomp.com">vmatonis@flucomp.com</a>.
		</p>
]]>
    </Content>
    <Content Name="Placeholder">
      <![CDATA[[Placeholder for content]]]>
    </Content>
  </Page>
  <Page Name="AboutUs">
    <Content Name="Placeholder">
      <![CDATA[[Placeholder for content]]]>
    </Content>
  </Page>
  <Page Name="Contact">
    <Content Name="Email">
      <![CDATA[<a href="mailto:inbox@flucomp.com">inbox@flucomp.com</a>]]>
    </Content>
    <Content Name="Phone">(708) 529-8725</Content>
    <Content Name="Twitter">
      <![CDATA[
			Follow us on Twitter: <a href="http://twitter.com/flucomp" target="_blank">@flucomp</a>
			]]>
    </Content>
    <Content Name="GooglePlus">
      <![CDATA[
			Add us to your circles on Google Plus: <a href="https://plus.google.com/100714296740064629468" target="_blank">Flucomp Enterprises, Inc.</a>
			]]>
      <!--logo attributed to Alice Olivier: http://www.vectorfree.com/g-logo-pack -->
    </Content>
    <Content Name="Manta">
      <![CDATA[<a href="http://www.manta.com/c/mml63m0/flucomp-enterprises-inc" target="_blank">
				<img src="http://www.manta.com/manta/images/mantaBadge_md.png" height="32" width="80" border="0" />
			</a>]]>
    </Content>
  </Page>
  <Page Name="Staff">
    <Person>
      <Name>Dr. Diana Matonis</Name>
      <Experience>25 years</Experience>
      <Position>President/CEO, Consultant</Position>
      <Title>Founder</Title>
      <Biography>
        <![CDATA[
				<p>
            <b>Reputation</b> 20-year track record of growing revenues, improving operations and managing/developing strategies to capture value in
            arrived solutions. I also formed and led Global Chemical Manufacturers and Oil &amp; Gas Joint Industry Partnerships.
            My work in Natural Gas Pipeline modeling has been globally recognized; I have been an internationally-invited presenter in peer-reviewed
            conferences and global Chemical Manufacturer and Oil &amp; Gas private corporate invitations, saving each company a 15-20% chemical cost per
            month savings.
        </p>
        <p>
            <b>Specialties</b> Energy Project Development / Management, Operations / Asset Management, economic analysis, 
            competitive analysis, statistical analysis, project management, financial analysis, business strategy, strategic planning, 
            new technology development, managing budgets determining headcount requirements, working with contractors, 
            writing technical specifications, developing software tools, working with suppliers and reviewing supplier designs, 
            diagnosing customer equipment, working with production on problem solving and trouble shooting, and developing detailed test programs.
        </p>]]>
      </Biography>
      <Picture>~/Include/img/pic/diana_actual.png</Picture>
      <Email>dmatonis@flucomp.com</Email>
      <FullBioLink>https://www.linkedin.com/in/matonis/</FullBioLink>
    </Person>
    <Person>
      <Name>Vince Matonis</Name>
      <Experience>6 years</Experience>
      <Position>Software Engineer, Systems Administrator, Consultant</Position>
      <Title>IT Director</Title>
      <Biography>
        <![CDATA[Software Developer for 6 years. <br />
				Programming experience: C#, C/C++, Java <br />
				Web Development experience: ASP.NET/C#, PHP/MySQL, HTML4&amp;HTML5, CSS2&amp;CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery]]>
      </Biography>
      <Picture>~/Include/img/pic/vince_new_4_4.png</Picture>
      <Email>vmatonis@flucomp.com</Email>
      <FullBioLink>https://www.linkedin.com/in/vmatonis/</FullBioLink>
    </Person>
  </Page>
  <Page Name="Portfolio">
    <Content Name="Index">
      <![CDATA[<h3>Examples of our Work</h3>
		<table id="portfolio_index">
			<tbody>
				<tr>
					<td class="ptitle">
						Engineering
					</td>
					<td class="pdesc">
						<p>
							Independent consulting includes projects in the fields of biomass pyrolysis plant optimization and 
						economics, chemical analyses and process development with an initial pro-forma analysis, new development 
						processes and technology training and research assistance in the area of  thermal plasma pyrolysis 
						process for converting waste to fuels, and the integration of fuel cells within existing Power Plants 
						at Fuel Cell Energy. 
						</p>
						<p>
							For example, we improved the quality, and consistency and yield of product for a startup biofuels 
							company using a new integrated pyrolytic process for obtaining saturated and unsaturated alkyl 
							esters from biomass. to consistently produce biodiesel grade product.
						</p>
					</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td class="ptitle">
						Software
					</td>
					<td class="pdesc">
						Our custom software includes the successful completion of a major stand-alone software package
						called Pipecalc: a calculator for the properties of polypropylene pipeline installations, both 
						subterranean and above-ground.
					</td>
				</tr>
			</tbody>
		</table>]]>
    </Content>
  </Page>
</Content>